Guide to the Lolo National Forest Collection 1894-1987
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Photographic Materials, 1894-1987; Series VI; 351 images
  - Old Glory floats abouve Ninemile CCC camp (F-36) at Huson, Montana in the Lolo National Forest, circa 1930s; Believed to be Camp Menard; Photo courtesy of Bob Croskry (Box 19, Photo number 94-4744)
  - Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1930s; Photo courtesy of Bob Croskrey (Box 19, Photo number 94-4745)
  - Old Glory floats abouve Ninemile CCC camp (F-36) at Huson, Montana in the Lolo National Forest, circa 1930s; Same as 94-4744 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4746)
  - A winter scene at the Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1930s; Same as 94-4742 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4747)
  - Ninemile CCC camp gym, circa 1930s; Annex: library and education. Photo courtesy of Bill Perusich (Box 19, Photo number 94-4748)
  - A winter scene at the Ninemile CCC camp #3, circa 1930s; Same as 94-4743 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4749)
  - Many miles of pole and jack leg fence built by Ninemile CCC crews, circa 1930s; Photo courtesy of Bill Perusich (Box 19, Photo number 94-4750)
  - CCC irrigation ditch project for Ninemile Remount Depot pastures, circa 1930s; Photo courtesy of Reman Paul Temple (Box 19, Photo number 94-4751)
  - Flume to transfer water from Butler Creek to Stoney Creek, undated; Photo courtesy of Bill Perusich (Box 19, Photo number 94-4752)
  - Building at Ninemile, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4753)
  - Building at Ninemile, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4754)
  - Building at Ninemile, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4755)
  - Building at Ninemile, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4756)
  - Interior fireplace of building at Ninemile, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4757)
  - Ralph and Bruce Thisted and horses moving a large stack of hay, 1942; Photo labeled "Blue Ridge." View looking north from field northwest of old ranch buildings (Box 19, Photo number 94-4758)
  - Several long tables set up for Show Me Day, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 94-4759)
  - Farrier at Show Me Day, Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s; Photo courtesy of Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4760)
  - Farrier at Show Me Day, Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s; Photo courtesy of Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4761)
  - Two men and a dog at Show me Day, circa 1930s; Forestry supplies in the background (Box 19, Photo number 94-4762)
  - Show Me Day, circa 1930s; Man on the left is Arthur Stone, Dean of the School of Journalism at the Unversity of Montana; woman is a reporter for the Missoulian (Box 19, Photo number 94-4763)
  - Regional Forester, Major Evan Kelley, at Show Me Day, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 94-4764)
  - Crowd at Show Me Day, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 94-4765)
  - Old stock truck (REO Speedwagon, used until 1936-1937), circa 1930s; Man on right is Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4766)
  - Plow unit, 1932 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4767)
  - Unloading mules, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4767a)
  - First stock truck at Ninemile Remount Depot (1930 REO Speedwagon), circa 1931-1933; Driver: Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4768)
  - Loading old truck at Ninemile, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4768a)
  - Clyde Fickes at Fort Missoula, circa 1930s; CCC days (Box 19, Photo number 94-4769)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, 1934; Placer mining districts: Josphine Creek, McCormick Creek, Kennedy Creek, Butler Creek shown (Box 19, Photo number 94-4770)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, 1964 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4771)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, undated; Aerial view, Line 9 West (Box 19, Photo number 94-4772)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, undated; Aerial view, Line 11 East (Box 19, Photo number 94-4773)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, undated; Aerial view, Line 9 West (Box 19, Photo number 94-4774)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, undated; Aerial view, Line 11 East (Box 19, Photo number 94-4775)
  - Topo resource photos, Ninemile Ranger District, undated; Aerial view, Line 11 East (Box 19, Photo number 94-4776)
  - Halters and lead ropes, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4777)
  - Halters and lead ropes, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4778)
  - Halters and lead ropes, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4779)
  - Halters and lead ropes, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4780)
  - Halters and lead ropes, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4781)
  - Halters, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4782)
  - Halters, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4783)
  - Halters, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4784)
  - Three men resting, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4785)
  - Ninemile landscape, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4786)
  - Ninemile landscape, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4787)
  - Ninemile landscape, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4788)
  - Horse and pasture, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4789)
  - Horse and pasture, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4790)
  - Horse and pasture, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4791)
  - Mules and pasture, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4792)
  - Mules and pasture, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4793)
  - Mules, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4794)
  - Mules, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4795)
  - Mules, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4796)
  - Mules, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4797)
  - Mules, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4798)
  - Corral at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4799)
  - Corral at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4800)
  - Corral at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4801)
  - Corral at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4802)
  - Corral at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4803)
  - Corral at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4804)
  - Horseshoe in fire pit, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4805)
  - Horseshoe in fire pit, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4806)
  - Horseshoe in fire pit, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4807)
  - Horseshoe and anvil, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4808)
  - Horseshoe and anvil, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4809)
  - Blacksmith and tongs, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4810)
  - Blacksmith and tongs, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4811)
  - Blacksmith and tongs, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4812)
  - Blacksmith and tongs, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4813)
  - Blacksmith and tongs, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4814)
  - Saddle, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4815)
  - Feed bags, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4816)
  - Halters and lead ropes, 1977 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4817)